very easy to get a health insurance plan today, there are still
some ailments that basic health
insurance policies don't cover, such as
cancer, heart attack, kidney failure, and extra health insurance. To
cover these ailments, health
insurance companies have created critical illness
policies. Critical illness policies
specifically cover life-threatening diseases.
This policy allows the insured to
focus on their recovery without the stress of retirement. The basic
critical illness insurance plans
available in India include: Adv PCR Co Health,
Optima Vital One Max, Bupa Critical Illness Policy,
HDFC Ergo Critical Illness
Policy, Edelweiss Critical Illness Policy,
HDFC Life Cancer Airplane, Manipal
Signal Ideal Protection Critical Care
Plan, Reliance Critical Illness Policy, Ek Oni
Cancer Plan, Rally Critical Illness
Insurance Plan. You
can check the minimum and maximum entries, minimum and maximum combination options, policy term and waiting period of all these plans in the chart provided. First Sd
Senior Co Health  Optima Fighter Plane
covers all these illnesses
[music]
The second Maths Book Airplane
covers coconut feel
[music]
The third HDFC Ergo Critical Illness
Policy covers all misuse The
fourth Edelweiss Khatik Airplane covers all
certainty The fourth
HDFC Life Cancer
Airplane covers all these.
One of the plans, Manipal Signal Rifle Protection
Critical Care Plan,
covers all these critical illnesses. Seventh Reliance
Critical Illness Policy has all these categories.
Its English word is
98100 Cancer Plan is designed to cover every type of cancer and its
stage.
Ninth Rally Critical Illness Insurance
Plan covers all these critical illnesses.
Now let's talk about how to choose the
best plan for yourself from all these plans. The
first step to finding the right plan for you is to
review the board.
Considering the critical illness in your family history,
you should make a semi-final match of the right amount for yourself.
You
should compare different lenses and make a list of which company's plan is
giving you good claim settlement ratio at an affordable premium. Please share
that in the pursuit of low premium, you should
make a plan with low claim ratio. If you believe us,
the higher the calibration, the
easier it will be for you to get a claim in the future. If
you have any questions related to critical illness in these channels, then do
ask in the comment box below and along with
subscribing to our channel Politics, do
press the bell icon
so that you do not miss our latest videos. Make it
MP3